agriseek.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy policy - AgriSeek.com

AgriSeek.com - Serving agriculture since 2002

_Overview_   
AgriSeek.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply AgriSeek.com site. To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every AgriSeek.com employee. We also are conducting periodic and random reviews of our Web site and other products and services. 

_Collecting and Using Personal Information_  
When you visit and navigate our site and when you communicate with us via our site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. Any non-public personal information that you may provide via our site will be used solely for the purpose stated on the page where it is collected. AgriSeek.com will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of AgriSeek.com. and its affiliated companies unless (a) expressly authorized by you, or (b) required or permitted by law. In all cases, we will disclose the information consistent with applicable laws and regulations and we will require the recipient to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.   
By “personal information,” we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, social security number, or telephone number. From time to time, we may request personal information from you at our sites in order to deliver requested materials to you, respond to your questions, or deliver a product or service. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or other business partners. PLEASE BE AWARE that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (such as your name, e-mail address) in chat areas or bulletin boards to third parties, that information may be collected by others outside the control of us and may result in unsolicited messages from others. 

_Children's_  
AgriSeek.com is committed to the safety of our children. Children under 18 may not participate in any sweepstakes or contests on AgriSeek.com. Also, we encourage children under the age of 18 to ask a parent for permission before providing or sending any information to anyone on-line. 

_Other Information; "Cookies"_  
Like most commercial websites, we may also use what is known as “cookie” technology. A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to your browser when you link to that website. It is not a computer program and has no ability to read data residing on your computer or instruct it to perform any step or function. By assigning a unique data element to each visitor, the website is able to recognize repeat users, track usage patterns and better serve you when you return to our site. The cookie does not extract other personal information about you, such as your name or address. Most browsers provide a simple procedure that will enable you to control whether you want to receive cookies by notifying you when a website is about to deposit a cookie file. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

_Security of Information_  
We use our best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. AgriSeek.com has adopted and adheres to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public personal information at AgriSeek.com against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We periodically subject our site to simulated intrusion tests and have developed comprehensive disaster recovery plans.

_Links to Other Sites_  
AgriSeek.com Web site may contain links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) is not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information.

_Data Sharing And Transfer_  
Your personal information will generally be stored in the AgriSeek.com databases, which are located mainly in the Canada or Europe, data may be transferred within AgriSeek.com across state or country borders. This may be done to consolidate data storage and simplify the management of customer information. 

_Choice/Opt-Out_  
AgriSeek.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. Users may remove their information from our database in order to not receive future communications by editing their Account Profile. If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. AgriSeek.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. AgriSeek.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact AgriSeek.com support to request the removal of this information from database.

_Questionnaires and Surveys_  
We may occasionally ask visitors to complete surveys and opinion polls about their attitudes and interests. Surveys help us to understand your needs. If sample answers to surveys are posted on the website site, no personally identifiable information will be included. If you participate in one of our surveys, you can be assured that we do not maintain any personal information about you in our databases as a result of the survey. 

_Changes to This Statement_  
We're always looking for ways to improve our site's features and services. As a result, this statement is updated from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on privacy practices at AgriSeek.com. This Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

_Your Acceptance of Our Privacy Practices_  
By using this website, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, and you adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the website.

_Third Party Advertising_  
AgriSeek.com use third-party advertising companies including Google, among others, to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit on our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

_Questions or comments? Please contact us_  
For questions, comments or assistance with any privacy-related issues, we invite you to [contact us.](https://www.agriseek.com/contact_us_email.php?TOPIC=7) We're always happy to help. 

For terms of use, please [click here](https://www.agriseek.com/terms.php).
